Benjamin Gerner

PROFILE

I'm a personal trainer who specializes in CrossFit and Tai Chi. I am also a full time college student in Integrative Physiology at the University of Colorado at Boulder. Finally, I am a qualified a full-stack web developer specializing in CSS, JavaScript, and React.

EXPERIENCE

PERSONAL TRAINER, GERNER FITNESS (SELF-EMPLOYED), CA — 2020-PRESENT

I have trained clients with a variety of ages, shapes, goals, and limitations. I run all of my clients through assessments to see what muscles of theirs are over-active and underactive. Next, I write a fully customized fitness regimen for them that not only includes specific exercises with weights and rep ranges, but also some meditative component as well as pre/ post- workout recovery exercises including stretches, rolling and lacrosse ball.

DRIVER, DOORDASH, CA - 2020-2021

I've completed over 150 deliveries and gotten no ratings lower than 5.0 stars. Based on customer feedback, I'm especially proficient with order handling and friendliness;)

MATH TUTOR, SELF-EMPLOYED, CA - 2017-2019

I reached out to people in my community via 'Next Door' during the first half of my sophomore year in high school and began tutoring local middle schoolers in either Pre-Algebra or Algebra. I continued to tutor in Algebra, and got another client who needed help with Geometry. I stopped tutoring at the end of my junior year.

WAREHOUSE/ FULFILLMENT, EMORO INC., CA — 2016-2021

Emoro Inc is a company that provides branded merchandise to corporations worldwide. I work there during the summers, mainly in the warehouse, organizing products, making/packing/shipping packages, and counting inventory.

EDUCATION

Marin Catholic High School (2020) — 5 on AP tests - Physics C: Mechanics, Calculus, Stats

NASM (2020) — Certified Personal Trainer

Colorado Outward Bound School (2020) — Certified Wilderness First Aid

UC Berkeley Extension (2021) — Coding Bootcamp: Full Stack Web Development

Many Currents (2021) — Tai Chi - Lee's Modified Chang Style Routine

University of Colorado at Boulder (present)